vamachina.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy policy | VAMA China

**1\. Personal data**

Non-personal and aggregated information collected automatically 

When you visit our Site, non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of VAMA’s Internet servers, in order to monitor and enhance your online experience. Such recorded information may include (without being limited to) your IP address, the name of your internet service provider, the operating system and the type of browser you used, the date and duration of your visit, the name(s) of the visited page(s), the amount of transferred data. 

Personal information that you choose to submit 

As a general policy, you are not required to disclose your personal data as a condition of using this Web Site. No personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to the Web Site. 

However, VAMA Web Site’s various registration forms and surveys may request that you give us contact information (such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address) and profile data (such as your preferences). In many cases, you choose the amount of information you supply (e.g. when sending us information through the Site, you may choose to include only an e-mail address for replies). There may be cases, however, where some of the information requested is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. In such cases, if you do not provide mandatory personal information with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

If you request information through this Web Site and supply VAMA with your e-mail address or your name and postal address, you accept that this data will be used for the purpose of providing the requested information and that VAMA may use this data in the future to provide other information about VAMA that might be of interest to you. 

You have the right to consult your personal data, to correct your personal data, if necessary, and to withdraw your consent to the use of your personal data. For this purpose you may contact VAMA at the following address: 

VAMA 

Address: No. 88, North Ji Xing Road, Loudi Economic Development Zone, Loudi, Hunan, China 

Tel: (+86) 738 8688 010 

Email: [contactus@vamachina.com](mailto:contactus@vamachina.com "Contact VAMA")

Fax: (+86) 738 8688 010 

Zip code: 417000 

Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties outside of VAMA group. VAMA may disclose user information in special cases when we have reasons to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with VAMA’s rights or property, other users of the Web Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

**2\. Careers**

If you apply for jobs through the Web Site, you accept that the application will be processed either by VAMA or by the relevant subsidiary within the VAMA group. VAMA or the relevant subsidiary will use the personal data supplied by the applicants for the purpose of processing the application. Applicants have the right to consult their personal data, to correct the personal data, if necessary, and to withdraw their consent to the use of their personal data. For this purpose applicants may contact the recipient of the application at the e-mail address to which they have sent the application or to [jobs@vamachina.com](mailto:jobs@vamchina.com) if the application was made via the “Job opportunities section. 

**3\. Use of cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Sites easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Sites, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. (Note: you will need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions.) If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of VAMA Web Sites will not function properly or may be considerably slower. 

**4\. Use of IP addresses**

An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet provider whenever you’re surfing the Web. When you request pages from VAMA’s Web Site, our servers log your IP address. VAMA collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to audit the use of our Site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you are anonymous to us. We may exceptionally use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Sites, customers, or others. 

**5\. Security**

Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, VAMA cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**6\. Contact:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings with our Sites, you can contact: VAMA [contactus@vamachina.com](mailtoa: contactus@vamachina.com "Contact VAMA"). 

Information provided by you via general e-mail inquiries to VAMA such as your e-mail address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties. 

**7\. General:**

You may not assign these Terms of Use or any of your interests, rights or obligations under these Terms of Use. If any provision of these Terms of Use is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition. 

**8\. Jurisdiction:**

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, YOU HEREBY EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT ANY PROCEEDINGS ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO YOUR USE OF THE WEB SITE, ITS INFORMATION, SERVICES AND CONTENT SHALL BE SUBJECT TO THE LAWS OF CHINA. THE COURTS IN CHINA SHALL HAVE EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION.
